Guide to the Stanford University, Office of the Vice Provost for Teaching & Learning, records SC1293
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Records, Accession ARCH_2016_122
  - Audiovisual materials
    - John Perry, 1999 Feb 11; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Donald Kennedy, 1999 Jan 21; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Kelly Skeff, 1999; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Len Ortolano, 1999; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Sam Chin, 1998 Nov 12; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Dennis Mathies, 1998 Nov 5; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Condoleeza Rice, 1998 Oct 22; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Christina Maslach, 1998 May 14; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Robert Waymouth, 1998 Apr 23; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Paul Turner, 1998 Feb 28; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Diane Middlebrook, 1998 Feb 12; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Robert McCain, 1998 Jan 22; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Estelle Freedman, 1997 Nov 20; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - John Taylor, 1997 Nov 13; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - James Gibbs, 1997 Oct 16; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Sandy Fetter, 1997 May 11; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Russell Fernald, 1997 May 1; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Barbara Gelp, 1997 Apr 17; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Russell Fernald, 1997 Feb 7; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - David Kennedy, 1997 Nov 23; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Al Camarillo, 1997 May 22; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - John Richford, 1996 Nov 21; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Luis Fraga, 1996 Nov 7; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Brigette Cazellas, 1996 Oct 10; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Anne Fernald, 1996 May 2; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Par Jones, 1996 Apr 18; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Jon Kranitz, 1996 Feb 15; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Sanford Dornbusch, 1996 Jan 25; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Doug Oschoof, 1995 Nov 30; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - James Mar, 1995 Oct 12; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Harry Elam, 1995 Mar 25; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Susan McConnell, 1995 May 4; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Sherri Sheppard, 1995 Feb 16; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Gil Masters, 1995 Mar 2; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - John Bravman, 1995 Feb 2; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Brad Osgood, 1995 Nov 19; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Barbara Gelpi, 1993; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Paul Simon 1 of 2, 2013 Jun 7; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Econ 1 Constantine Yannelis, 2013 Oct 24; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - unlabeled, 2013 May 23; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Art History 1 George LeBourdais, 2013 Nov 1; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Paul Simon 2 of 2, 2013 Aug 7; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - R. Kirkwood Eng 146, 2013 Jun 6; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Anna Marshall Spanlang, 2013 Mar 15; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - John Richford, 2013 May 13; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - S. Lee, 2013 Apr 16; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - John Bouthroya tape 1 of 2, 2013 May 14; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Wei Peng, 2013 May 22; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - John Bouthroya tape 2 of 2, 2013 May 14; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Dean Claude Steele tape 2/3, 2013 Jan 31; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Dean Claude Steele tape 1/3, 2013 Jan 31; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Carol Boggs, 2012 Nov 1; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Robert Siegel, 2012 May 10; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Jennifer Summit, 2012 Feb 2; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - S. Crane, 2013 Apr 17; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Clare Robinson, 2010 Dec 1; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Andrea Lunsford, 2011 Oct 13; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Gabriella Safron, 2011 May 19; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Ralph Cohen, 2011 Feb 10; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Dr. Elam, 1020 Jan 9; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Orientation, 2010 Sep 17; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 3)
    - Margot Gerritsen, 2012 Jan 26; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 5)
    - Robertson Hartley Conetr, 2011 Nov 3; 1 videotape(s) (1 videotape(s) (minidv)) (Box 5)
    - Michele Marincovich "How to give an academic job talk", 2000 Jan 26; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
    - Effective teaching, good and bad mixed, how not to TA, 2001; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
    - Race in the Classroom: the multiplicity of experience, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
    - Professor Russell Fernald " how to design and teach a new course", 1997 May 1; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
    - Professor John Bravman "Five Essential Concepts for Successful Lecturing, 1995 Feb 2; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
    - Professor Russell Fernald " how to design and teach a new course", 1997; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
    - Opening Doors: Two cases of Formative Assessment of Teaching, 1996; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
    - TA Orientation, 2004 Apr 1; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
    - Teaching with Style, 1996 Oct 18; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
    - Teachers on Teaching with Orr, 2000; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
    - Professor Russell Fernald " how to design and teach a new course", 1997 May 1; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
    - Part 2, electrical engineering TA orientation, 1996 Sep 23; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
    - EE Orientation tape 2, 1995; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
    - Prof. John Etchemendy, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
    - CTL orientation, 2000 Sep 26; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
    - TA Orientation - Effective Teaching, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
    - Resources for TA's, 2000 Jan 4; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
    - Gene Suarez - Writing and Identity, 1992 Apr 20; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
    - 25th Anniversary, 2000 Nov 21; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
    - How to Give a Lecture with David Kennedy, 1997 Jan; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
    - Effective Teaching: an Illustration of Techniques, 1989; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
    - How not to TA, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
    - Teleconference with Ohio State University preparing teaching assistants, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
    - Live and Learn, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
    - Close encounters of the academic kind, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
    - Designing and teaching your own course, 1991 Sep 24; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
    - A Final Line: Advice to Stanford TA's about sexual harrassment (excerpt), 1998 Sep; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
    - Professor Laura Carstensen "teaching critical thinking about gender", 2003 Feb 27; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
    - Being a Machine vs. Being Curious: what do students want?, 1998 Nov; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
    - Electrical Engineering TA orientation, part 2, 1997 Sep 22; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
    - Electrical Engineering TA orientation, part 1, 1997 Sep 22; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
    - Interactive Teaching Robyn Dunbar, 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 7)
    - Thinking Together Collaborative learning in science disc 1, 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 7)
    - Simplifying for Clarity, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
    - Adapting to Students, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
    - Clarity of Explanations in natural science and engineering courses, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
    - Effective lecturing: getting students' attention, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
    - Effective lecturing: getting students' attention, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
    - unlabeled, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
    - Effective lecturing: getting students' attention, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
    - Effective lecturing: getting students' attention, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
    - Effective lecturing: engaging students, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
    - Effective lecturing: engaging students, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
    - Clarity of Explanations: linking, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
    - Adapting to Students, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
    - Classroom Environment, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
    - Classroom Environment, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
    - Simplifying for Clarity, 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
    - CTL event photos, 2004 Nov; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-R) (Box 14)
    - Robert Sayler, 2008 May 5; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 14)
    - Rod Searcey, 2004 May; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-R) (Box 14)
    - PRS-Burchat, 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 14)
    - Inan Remixed, 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 14)
    - Prof. Inan AWTT low volume, 2009 Apr 20; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 14)
    - Watering the Farm: Stanford's water systems old and new, near and far David Freyberg, 2010 Oct 13; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 14)
    - CTL event photos, 2006 Jun; 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 14)
    - Teaching Awards, 2004 Jun 12; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-R) (Box 14)
    - CTL event photos, 2006 Nov; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-R) (Box 14)
    - Deborah Gordon, Coit Blacher, Rod Searcey photos, 2005; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-R) (Box 14)
    - CTL, 2004 Jan 22; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-R) (Box 14)
    - Rod Searcey, 2008 Apr 23; 1 optical disc(s) (CD-R) (Box 14)
    - Academic Job talk, 1 optical disc(s) (CD-R) (Box 14)
    - misc. photos, 1 optical disc(s) (CD-R) (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - award winning teachers on teaching master 1 optical disc(s) (DVD)s, 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 14, Folder 2)